Guide to the Civic Education Project records, 1992-2004
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 9: Conference Materials (chronological), 1995-2003; (3.5 boxes)
  - Caucasus 5th Regional Student Conference: Caucasus Today: Same Problems; Alternative Solutions, Tbilisi, Georgia, March, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - 8th Annual Balkan Debate Forum, Montenegro, April, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Colloquium: The Study of the Holocaust in Recent Romanian Historiography, Bucharest, June, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Series 10: Photos/Slides, 1991-2004; (8 boxes)
  - Stifin, CSFR, September, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Thanksgiving, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Orientation, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - JAN Conference, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Selection Meeting, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Prague Meeting, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Recruiting, Fall, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Vienna Student Conference, Folder 1, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Vienna Student Conference, Folder 2, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Lviv, Ukraine CEP Conferences, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - CEP UK Student Conferences, March, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Poland Retreat, 1995-1996 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Orientation, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Baltics, 1996-1997 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Board Meeting, February, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Active Learning Workshop, Szeged, Hungary, May, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Student Conference, Ukraine, September, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Hillary Clinton, Novosibirsk, November, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - CD Meetings, Fall, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - International Student Conference, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - RNAP, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Orientation, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Balkan Debate Forum, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - 4th Annual BDF, Bishiza, Bulgaria, May, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - 4th Annual BDF, Bishiza, Bulgaria, November, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - ESRT, Budapest, Hungary, December, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - ISC, Budapest, Hungary, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - New Haven Orientation, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Balkans, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Junior Academies Conference, Bucharest, Romania, February, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Workshop, Yerevan, Armenia, Spring, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Student Conference on European Integration, Sofia, Bulgaria, April, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Balkan Debate Forum, May, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Fellows, 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Career Fair, Vienna, Austria, April, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Conference, Moldova State University, December, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Conferences, Kharkov and Kiev, Ukraine, 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - SEE-SE CD Meeting, Prague, Czech Republic, January, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - CEP Meeting, February, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - 7th BDF, Herceg Novi, Montenegro, March, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Romanian Retreat, February, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - CD Meeting, Budapest, Hungary, April, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - BUM Meeting, Ukraine, August, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Office Party, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Spring CD meeting, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Regional Student Conference, Almaty, Kazakhstan, March, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Central Asia and Mongolian Debate Forum, Issak-Koh, Kyrgyzstan, April, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - 2nd Annual Saratov Russian American Education Fair (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - International Student Conference, Vienna, Austria (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Bulgarian Debate Forum (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Thanksgiving Party (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Meeting Photos (with negatives), Undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Meeting Photos (with negatives), Undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Meeting Photos (with negatives), Undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - City and Scenic Shots, Undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Bulgaria, 1991, 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Prague, Czech Republic, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Estonia, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Southern Estonia, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Budapest, Hungary (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Pecs, Hungary, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Latvia (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Vilnius, Lithuania (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Macedonia (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Romania (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Ukraine (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Annual Report Photos, 2000-2001 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Photos (8x10), Folder 1 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Photos (8x10), Folder 2 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Country Director Photos (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Group Photos, Undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Staff and Office Photos (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Photos (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Photos, Phil Henderson, Undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Meeting and Event Photos, Folder 1 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Meeting and Event Photos, Folder 2 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Meeting and Event Photos, Folder 3 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Meeting and Event Photos, Folder 4 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Meeting and Event Photos, Folder 5 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Meeting and Event Photos (Large) (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Slides, Folder 1 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Slides, Folder 2 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Slides, Poland (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Negatives (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - 1 CEP 3rd Annual Balkan Debate Forum, Romania, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - A/M/K-Bulgaria/Macedonia Joint Retreat, November, 10-13, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - CEP, 1999-2000 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Russia 5th Anniversary Student Conference, St. Petersburg (May 15-17, 1999), Poland-Baltics Orientation and Romania Orientation (Sept. 2000), and Bulgaria Macedonia Orientation (Sept. 2000)
  - Conferences, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Student Conference Budapest (May 5-10, 2000), CD Meeting (Oct. 25-30, 2000) and Anglo American College Student Conference, Prague (Dec. 1-3 2000)
  - Bulgaria Roundtables, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    5 SEE Roundtable and Orientation, Bulgaria (2001) and EU Studies Roundtable, Sofia, Bulgaria (Feb., 2001)
  - Forums, March-April, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    Caucasus Debate Forum, Tbilisi (March 2001), CD Meeting (March-April 2001)
  - ISC Budapest, April, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - ISC Budapest, April, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - ISC Budapest, April, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Orientations and Debate Forum, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    Czech/Slovakia Orientation (Sept. 2001), Albania/Montenegro/Serbia Orientation (Sept. 2001) and Belgrade, Serbia and Balkan Debate Forum, Romania (2001)
  - Orientations, 2001-2002 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    Orientation (2001), Conference, "Critical Sociology: Perspectives on Society and Sociology, Tbilisi, Georgia (June, 2002) and SEE Orientation, Budapest, Hungary (Sept. 2002)
  - 2nd Annual Balkan Debate Forum, 1997 May 9-12 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - CD Meeting, Budapest, 8-14, August, 2002 (Box 25)
    Light Blue Canister
  - Caucasus Debate Forum, Tbilisi, 16-19, March, 2001 (Box 25)
    4 Clear Canister
  - Conference (Box 25)
    2 - no information
  - Red Canister, Undated (Box 25)
    6
  - Fellows Retreat In Romania, 19-19, April, 2002 (Box 25)
  - Clear Canister, Undated (Box 25)
    2
  - Yellow Canister, Undated (Box 25)
  - Retreat in Romania, 16-19, April, 2002 (Box 25)
    Light Blue
  - 7th Balkan Debate Forum, Hercep Novi, Montenegro, 4-9, March, 2002 (Box 25)
  - Christmas Party, CEP, December, 2001 (Box 25)
  - SEE Roundtable, Sofia, Bulgaria, 16-18, February, 2001 (Box 25)
  - SEE Orientation, Budapest, Hungary, 2002 (Box 25)
  - Christmas Party, 2000 (Box 25)
  - ISC, Budapest, 24-29, April, 2001 (Box 25)
    4
  - SEE Roundtable, Sofia, Bulgaria, 15-18 (II), February, 2001 (Box 25)
  - BDF Timisora, Belgrade, Serbia, 2001 (Box 25)
  - Albania, Kosovo, Montenegro, Serbia Orientation, Montenegro, 22-25, September, 2001 (Box 25)
  - Miscellaneous slides, Slovakia, Russia (Box 25)
- Series 11: Other Media, 1994-2004; (1 box)
  - Corporate PowerPoint Presentation (Box 26, Folder 1)
    Computer disc and hardcopy
  - Western Europe Office Documents (Box 26, Folder 2)
    Zip disc
  - Audiotape, March 18, 2003 (Box 26)
    Radio Interview with Gasan Guseinov about the CEP-Bosch Conference theme St. Petersburg, March 2003
  - VHS Tape, labeled The School Drama (Box 26)
  - VHS Tape, labeled Civic Education Project-Bulgaria, Fifth Annual Student Balkan Debate Forum, May 12-14, 2000 (Box 26)
    Sofia, Bulgaria, Debate Sessions: "Political and Economic Globalization Has Positive Effects on Balkan Countries", and "NATO's Action In Yugoslavia Resulted in Deeper Cleavages within the Balkan Region"
  - VHS Tape, labeled Civic Education Project-Bulgaria, Fifth Annual Student Balkan Debate Forum, May 12-14, 2000 (Box 26)
    Sofia, Bulgaria, Debate Session: "The Creation of Ethnically Homogenous States In the Balkans is the Only Way to Achieve a Peaceful Co-existence in the Region", and "Changes on the 90s Have Increased Opportunities for Young Women in Balkan Countries"
  - VHS Tape, labeled Civic Education Project-Bulgaria, Fifth Annual Student Balkan Debate Forum, May 12-14, 2000 (Box 26)
    Sofia, Bulgaria, Debate Session "Balkan Countries' Economic Prosperity is Impossible without Substantial Foreign Aid", and Final Country Presentations
  - VHS Tape, labeled Student Conference, Budapest, May, 2000 (Box 26)
    2 copies
  - VHS Tape, labeled Central and Eastern European Moot Ct, Ljubljana, 2000 (Box 26)
  - VHS Tape, labeled Orientation 97-98, 1997-1998 (Box 26)
  - VHS Tape, labeled Orientation 97-98 RNAP, 1997-1998 (Box 26)
  - CD Annual Report, July, 1999 - June, 2000 (Box 26)
  - CD Annual Report, July, 2000 - June, 2001 (Box 26)
  - CD CEP Newsletter, Volume 6, Number 1, Academic Year 2000-1, 2000-2001 (Box 26)
  - CD Calendar Viewing Disc, May, 2001 (Box 26)
  - CD Calendar, 2002 (Box 26)
  - CD Donna AR Photos, 2001 (Box 26)
  - CD CEP Russia Photos (Box 26)
- Series 12: Memorabilia, 1992-2004; (1 box)
  - CEP T-Shirt (Box 27)
  - CEP Corporate Seal (Box 27)